version=1
lefttoright=true
author=Anita le Roux
numeric=false

The man almost called to the boy. I thought that something looked different. 
They all had time to get to know the children. When would he find what is important? 
She has many books to read for school. Even great men can be small. 
We look at the earth and it makes us think. Some people long for another world. 
He was waiting with his father or mother. From there the line goes off along the side again. 
Which name did you write on the paper? The animals still need their water and fresh air. 
We often used to go away to the country together. I have not asked who made each part and thing. 
But the sun keeps shining. They said there is more to this life than your work. 
What do you like about him? Will the boys come to hear the story? This old place is the best by miles. 
We wait until the last day. Your eyes are very kind. One year may sometimes seem to be without end. 
The words were in a sentence. At last we are going to live. 